{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262396902","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262396902"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" a3c11603-bf69-417d-8933-3195a2eeeb61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262411594","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262411594"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" a3c11603-bf69-417d-8933-3195a2eeeb61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262414309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262414308"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" a3c11603-bf69-417d-8933-3195a2eeeb61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262414442","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262414442"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" a3c11603-bf69-417d-8933-3195a2eeeb61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262424205","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262424205"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" a3c11603-bf69-417d-8933-3195a2eeeb61"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262435078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262435078"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" bbcefffa-44f2-48ba-ac8a-914c49995e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262436032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262436031"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" bbcefffa-44f2-48ba-ac8a-914c49995e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262443627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262443626"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" bbcefffa-44f2-48ba-ac8a-914c49995e43"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262454267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262454267"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 831dc175-a0f1-4f5d-8129-e0bcf410bcd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262455337","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262455337"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 831dc175-a0f1-4f5d-8129-e0bcf410bcd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262457956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262457956"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 831dc175-a0f1-4f5d-8129-e0bcf410bcd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262459019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262459019"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 831dc175-a0f1-4f5d-8129-e0bcf410bcd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262460489","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262460489"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 831dc175-a0f1-4f5d-8129-e0bcf410bcd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262460578","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262460578"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 831dc175-a0f1-4f5d-8129-e0bcf410bcd0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.lc.8__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262471878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262471877"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262472111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262472110"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262473084","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262473083"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262474366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262474365"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262477325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262477325"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262478183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262478182"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262478504","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262478504"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262479750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262479749"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262483366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262483365"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262484360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262484359"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262484623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262484623"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262485582","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262485580"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262488425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262488424"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262489458","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262489458"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262489930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262489930"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262494496","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262494494"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262494579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262494579"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 961895b9-888f-41f4-86a3-cb42b7b1d93d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_2"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262503200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262503200"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262505321","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262505320"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262507492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262507491"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262510705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262510704"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262512954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262512953"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262515193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262515192"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262518048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262518047"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262520239","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262520237"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262522479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262522478"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262525727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262525727"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262527835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262527834"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262529984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262529983"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262532982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262532982"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262535230","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262535228"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262537462","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262537462"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262540476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262540475"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262542825","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262542824"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262545168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262545168"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262548216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262548215"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262550420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262550419"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262552589","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262552588"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262555725","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262555725"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262557938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262557937"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262560122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262560121"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262563329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262563328"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262565730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262565729"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262568155","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262568154"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262571303","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262571302"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262573577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262573576"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262575870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262575870"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262578851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262578850"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262581089","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262581088"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262583331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262583330"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262586257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262586257"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262588658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262588658"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262591028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262591027"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262594173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262594172"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262596581","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262596580"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262598955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262598953"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262601938","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262601937"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262604252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262604251"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262606561","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262606560"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262609828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262609828"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262612098","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262612098"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262614346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262614346"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262617739","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262617738"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262620169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262620168"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262622615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262622614"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262625512","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262625512"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262627689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262627688"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262629860","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262629860"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262633263","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262633262"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262635593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262635592"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262637930","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262637929"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262641072","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262641071"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262643360","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262643360"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262645618","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262645617"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262648690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262648690"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262650834","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262650834"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262652950","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262652950"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262656043","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262656042"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262658305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262658305"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262660524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262660523"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262663707","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262663706"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262665944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262665944"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262668180","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262668179"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262671466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262671466"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262673823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262673822"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262676191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262676190"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262679314","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262679314"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262681673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262681672"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262684010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262684010"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262687402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262687400"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262687495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262687494"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" ad468ed1-d177-4c07-a6c3-865e85b5bfe3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262693516","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262693516"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" c3ffda8e-b0fb-46df-89ee-d48b53178fee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262706900","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262706899"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" c3ffda8e-b0fb-46df-89ee-d48b53178fee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262709525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262709525"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" c3ffda8e-b0fb-46df-89ee-d48b53178fee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262709695","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262709695"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" c3ffda8e-b0fb-46df-89ee-d48b53178fee"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262720905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262720903"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262729150","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262729150"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" START_CHUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262733709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262733708"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262735287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262735286"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262737729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262737729"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262739354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262739354"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262742307","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262742307"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262743936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262743935"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262746477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262746476"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262748065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262748064"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262753238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262753237"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262754828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262754827"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262757384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262757383"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262759009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262759008"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262763961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262763961"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262765559","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262765558"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262768129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262768128"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262769744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262769743"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262772379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262772379"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262773980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262773979"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262776790","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262776789"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262778831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262778829"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262778921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262778921"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 3e1934d5-fbed-46f5-82ed-ebf46c96b229"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262791954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262791953"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262800895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262800895"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" START_CHUNGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262804387","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262804387"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262805991","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262805991"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262810232","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262810232"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAI"," userResponse":" CHAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262811807","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262811807"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262814548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262814548"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262816159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262816158"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262818301","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262818300"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" choo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOO"," userResponse":" CHOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262819885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262819884"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262824460","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262824460"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chapati"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAPATI"," userResponse":" CHAPATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262826045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262826044"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262828408","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262828407"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262830030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262830030"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262834133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262834133"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262835762","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262835761"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262838141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262838141"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chombo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHOMBO"," userResponse":" CHOMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262839764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262839764"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262847758","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262847758"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chipsi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHIPSI"," userResponse":" CHIPSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262849418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262849417"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262855958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262855957"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262857986","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262857984"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262858247","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262858247"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 702e3c3f-026e-47be-91b8-dc907f91cb51"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262892893","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262892892"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262893756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262893755"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262894793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262894793"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262895046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262895045"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262895606","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262895606"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262896184","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262896184"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWENYE"," userResponse":" MWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262896731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262896730"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wakati mmoja palikuwa na mamba mwenye njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262900614","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262900613"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAFUTA"," userResponse":" ALITAFUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262901370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262901369"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262901771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262901770"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262902598","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262902597"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" POLE"," userResponse":" POLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262903685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262903684"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262904479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262904479"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alitafuta chakula pole pole tena kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262907756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262907756"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMBA"," userResponse":" MAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262909300","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262909300"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mamba anashambulia!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANASHAMBULIA"," userResponse":" ANASHAMBULIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262912312","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262912312"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADA"," userResponse":" BAADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262912577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262912577"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262912601","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262912600"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262912696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262912696"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 30688ec5-abb8-4f15-8ccc-86010eecff83"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_6"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baada ya hiyo hana njaa tena na anafurahi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262924009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262924009"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" dc5cf4d9-8071-44bf-91b3-44c48817eb76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-CH.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262924233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262924233"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" dc5cf4d9-8071-44bf-91b3-44c48817eb76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262924317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262924317"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" dc5cf4d9-8071-44bf-91b3-44c48817eb76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGU"," userResponse":" CHUNGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262969955","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262969954"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" dc5cf4d9-8071-44bf-91b3-44c48817eb76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262977624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262977624"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" dc5cf4d9-8071-44bf-91b3-44c48817eb76"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-CH.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chungu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262986948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262986948"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINA"," userResponse":" JINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262987411","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262987411"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LANGU"," userResponse":" LANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262987654","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262987654"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262988173","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262988173"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jina langu ni Simo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMO"," userResponse":" SIMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262991450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262991450"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262992456","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262992455"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARIFIKI"," userResponse":" MARIFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262993185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262993184"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nina marifiki wanne."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANNE"," userResponse":" WANNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262996292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262996291"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJINA"," userResponse":" MAJINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262996754","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262996754"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAO"," userResponse":" YAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262996940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262996939"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262997753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262997752"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZO"," userResponse":" ZIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262998689","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262998688"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" LELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262999651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262999650"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263000132","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263000132"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263000821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263000821"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Majina yao ni Zizo Lele Sisa na Ayanda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AYANDA"," userResponse":" AYANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263004159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263004158"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263004551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263004551"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263005367","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263005366"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZO"," userResponse":" ZIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263006369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263006368"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263007078","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263007077"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263007842","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263007842"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Zizo anapenda kucheza mpira."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263011001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263011000"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263011627","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263011626"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263012196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263012196"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" LELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263013293","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263013293"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263014449","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263014449"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Lele anapenda kuogelea."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGELEA"," userResponse":" KUOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263017755","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263017754"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263018177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263018176"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263018924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263018924"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263020135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263020134"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263020935","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263020935"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUCHEZA"," userResponse":" KUCHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263021933","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263021932"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" MCHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263022161","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263022161"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263023237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263023237"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Sisa anapenda kucheza mchezo wa kujificha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFICHA"," userResponse":" KUJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263026612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263026612"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263027329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263027329"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263028062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263028062"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AYANDA"," userResponse":" AYANDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263029325","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263029325"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAPENDA"," userResponse":" ANAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263030138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263030138"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki yangu Ayanda anapenda kusoma."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUSOMA"," userResponse":" KUSOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263033823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263033823"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAPENDA"," userResponse":" NAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263034631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263034630"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263035007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263035006"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITU"," userResponse":" VITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263036095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263036094"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VYOTE"," userResponse":" VYOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263037381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263037381"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANAVYOPENDA"," userResponse":" WANAVYOPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263038208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263038207"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Napenda kufanya vitu vyote wanavyopenda kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263042122","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263042121"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mpira na Zizo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NACHEZA"," userResponse":" NACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263042777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263042776"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mpira na Zizo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263043100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263043100"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mpira na Zizo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263043680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263043680"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mpira na Zizo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIZO"," userResponse":" ZIZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263047675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263047675"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOGELEA"," userResponse":" NAOGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263048208","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263048207"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENYE"," userResponse":" KWENYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263048812","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263048812"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BWAWA"," userResponse":" BWAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263049056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263049055"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263049424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263049424"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Naogelea kwenye bwawa na Lele."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LELE"," userResponse":" LELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263053334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263053334"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NACHEZA"," userResponse":" NACHEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263054037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263054037"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MCHEZO"," userResponse":" MCHEZO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263054181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263054181"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263055096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263055096"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJIFICHA"," userResponse":" KUJIFICHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263055379","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263055379"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263055993","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263055993"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nacheza mchezo wa kujificha na Sisa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SISA"," userResponse":" SISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263059135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263059134"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263059625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263059625"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263060317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263060316"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJOO"," userResponse":" NJOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263062845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263062845"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263063339","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263063339"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263063604","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263063604"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263064427","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263064427"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263067616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263067615"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAPENDA"," userResponse":" UNAPENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263068575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263068575"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263071392","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263071391"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263071503","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263071503"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f605e390-8225-412e-b093-4a23c3455464"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_7"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Unapenda nini?"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263089126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263089125"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263089511","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263089511"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263090006","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263090005"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263090365","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263090364"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263090784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263090783"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263091268","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263091267"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263091498","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263091497"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263094750","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263094749"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263094798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263094797"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263095524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263095523"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263095924","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263095923"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263096223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263096223"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263096436","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263096436"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263096639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263096639"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263096961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263096960"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263097196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263097196"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263100349","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263100349"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263100753","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263100753"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263103338","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263103338"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263103550","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263103549"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263103759","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263103759"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263107260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263107258"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263111059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263111058"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263112094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263112093"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263114821","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263114821"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263115207","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263115205"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263115698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263115697"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263116051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263116051"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263116463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263116463"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263116948","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263116947"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263117178","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263117177"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263120466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263120465"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263120513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263120512"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263121238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263121237"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263121641","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263121640"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263121940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263121940"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263122159","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263122158"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263122354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263122353"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263122670","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263122670"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263122894","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263122894"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263125535","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263125534"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263125633","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263125632"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" 9f1c59c8-5643-4714-a126-c982337fdf35"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263133508","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263133508"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" d93c2495-2108-423a-a8db-429418b9cd22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263154609","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263154609"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" d93c2495-2108-423a-a8db-429418b9cd22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263157296","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263157295"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" d93c2495-2108-423a-a8db-429418b9cd22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263157429","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263157429"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" d93c2495-2108-423a-a8db-429418b9cd22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263179193","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263179193"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f8f9dda4-4098-4dfd-8b0f-c3044858e13c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_ch_n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263186731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263186731"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f8f9dda4-4098-4dfd-8b0f-c3044858e13c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_u_ch_n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263194937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263194936"," userId":" 5B13002062"," sessionId":" 5B13002062_20190123_195304"," gameId":" f8f9dda4-4098-4dfd-8b0f-c3044858e13c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.10.rand.say.41"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_u_ch_n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}